const questionsHtml = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: 'What is HTML?',
        answer: 'A. Hypertext Markup Language',
        options: [
            'A. Hypertext Markup Language',
            'B. High Technical Markup Language',
            'C. Hyper Technical Modern Language',
            'D. Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: 'What does HTML define?',
        answer: 'C. Structure of Web Pages',
        options: [
            'A. Programming Language',
            'B. Styling of Web Pages',
            'C. Structure of Web Pages',
            'D. Behavior of Web Pages'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:3 ,
        question: 'The HTML <canvas> element is used to?',
        answer: 'C. draw graphics',
        options: [
            'A. Create draggable elements',
            'B. Manipulate data in Mysql',
            'C. draw graphics',
            'D. display database records'
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: 'What does the <p> tag represent in HTML?',
        answer: 'A. Paragraph',
        options: [
            'A. Paragraph',
            'B. Link',
            'C. Image',
            'D. Table'
        ]
    },
    
        {
            numb: 5,
            question: 'Who is making the Web standards?',
            answer: 'D. The World Wide Web Consortium',
            options: [
                'A. Microsoft',
                'B. Google',
                'C. Mozilla',
                'D. The World Wide Web Consortium'
            ]
        },
        
{
            numb: 6,
            question: 'What does the "async" attribute do when used with a script tag?',
            answer: 'C. Specifies that the script should be executed asynchronously',
            options: [
                'A. Specifies that the script should be executed immediately',
                'B. Specifies that the script should be executed synchronously',
                'C. Specifies that the script should be executed asynchronously',
                'D. Specifies that the script should be executed conditionally'
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 7,
            question: 'What is the purpose of the "data-" attribute in HTML5?',
            answer: 'A. To store custom data attributes for elements',
            options: [
                'A. To store custom data attributes for elements',
                'B. To define the layout structure of the webpage',
                'C. To specify the type of document being used',
                'D. To provide metadata for search engines'
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 8,
            question: 'What does the <iframe> tag do in HTML?',
            answer: 'D. Embeds another document within the current HTML document',
            options: [
                'A. Inserts a new paragraph into the document',
                'B. Defines a fixed-size container for data',
                'C. Creates a frame for displaying images',
                'D. Embeds another document within the current HTML document'
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 9,
            question: 'In HTML, what does the "scoped" attribute do when used with a style tag?',
            answer: 'B. Applies the styles only to the parent element and its children',
            options: [
                'A. Applies the styles globally to all elements in the document',
                'B. Applies the styles only to the parent element and its children',
                'C. Specifies that the styles should be applied conditionally',
                'D. Allows the styles to be overridden by other style rules'
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 10,
            question: 'What is the purpose of the "accesskey" attribute in HTML?',
            answer: 'C. Defines a keyboard shortcut to activate or focus on an element',
            options: [
                'A. Specifies the accessibility level of an element',
                'B. Sets the priority of the element for search engine optimization',
                'C. Defines a keyboard shortcut to activate or focus on an element',
                'D. Determines the order in which elements are displayed on the page'
            ]
        }
    ];
    

